<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Root xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<Row>
		<description> Reset</description>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154515</referencenumber>
		<title> Azure Architect III</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
		<url>https://jobs.dxc.technology/ShowJob/Id/478747/Azure-Architect-III/</url>
		<description>  ›  Azure Architect III - New Orleans, LA
Azure Architect III - New Orleans, LA
Apply Now &gt;&gt;    
Requisition ID : 51154515Posting Date : 12-21-2018Category : ES - SalesLocation : New Orleans, LA USSchedule : Full TimeJob Description:
ROLE :

Understand and transform business requirements into scalable/manageable solution architecture and design specifications
Lead and manage developers in the delivery of Microservices and Microservices-based solutions
Drive the specification of Architecture and design patterns for integration and Microservices Architectures and solutions
Define standards to guide architecture solution decisions for integration and Microservices solutions
Experience in leading and implementing technology prototypes, proof of concepts, and reference implementations for new technologies
Ability to work closely with other Solution Architects/Designers to ensure consistency and quality of solutions.
Continuous improvement and exploration of industry standards and technology advances.
SKILLS:

6+ years of Experience in IT Industry, defining and solutioning  Digital Applications encompassing Technical Architecture, Integration Architecture and Application Architecture
Advanced experience in the Architecture and design of complex business process solutions using BPM and related technologies
Experience in architecting complex cloud solutions with one or more of the following - AWS, Azure, Google Engine, Digital Ocean
Strong understanding of network and data center architecture, as well as application development methodologies
Hands-on experience architecting, designing and implementing Microservices solutions utilizing container-based technologies including Docker, Swarm, Compose and Kubernetes
Experience in creating and utilizing architecture and design patterns
Experience of advanced integration experience with enterprise integration products including TIBCO, WebMethods, Oracle, MuleSoft, IBM WebSphere, JBoss Fuse, WSO2, Apache Camel
Experience of advanced integration experience with industry standard messaging products including ActiveMQ, RabbitMQ, IBM/MQ, other JMS based products and Apache Kafka
Experience of designing APIs and service interfaces.
Advanced Experience with SOA (Service Oriented Architecture)/ESB (Enterprise Service Bus)

Apply Now &gt;&gt;       

</description>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51160102</referencenumber>
		<title> Azure Senior Technical Consultant</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
		<url>https://jobs.dxc.technology/ShowJob/Id/485770/Azure-Senior-Technical-Consultant/</url>
		<description>  ›  Azure Senior Technical Consultant - New Orleans, LA
Azure Senior Technical Consultant - New Orleans, LA
Apply Now &gt;&gt;    
Requisition ID : 51160102Posting Date : 1-3-2019Category : ES - ServicesLocation : New Orleans, LA USSchedule : Full TimeJob Description:
We are looking for a motivated Senior Technical Consultant for Azure to join DXC’s Azure Centre of Excellence.

The DXC Azure Centre of Excellence enables customers’ digital transformation journeys with best practices, innovation and technical leadership for adoption of Microsoft Azure services.

You will work as a member of the Azure CoE team and be responsible providing advice and technical consulting to our customers in the adoption of Azure.  In addition, you will contribute to the development of standards and accelerators for architecture, design and delivery of Azure services. You will also support DXC Azure offering and service delivery teams with guidance on applying these best practices.

Responsibilities:

Delivery of Azure technical consulting engagements for DXC customers
Technical leadership in architecture, development and deployment of Azure based solutions for DXC customers and offering teams
Develop IP, best practices and knowledge assets to be re-usable and shared by the Azure CoE
Participate in providing mentoring support and guidance to team members to help grow skills and capabilities of the CoE
Actively contribute to a culture of high performance, innovation and continuous improvement.
Education and experience:

10+ years of experience in architecting, developing and deploying enterprise solutions, with Microsoft technology stack preferred
2+ years of experience in designing and deploying solutions on Microsoft Azure platform and experience in workload migrations
Experience with public cloud platforms, including design, implementation and workload migration.
Application architecture and development experience preferred
Microsoft Azure certification strongly preferred
Bachelor's degree or equivalent combination of education and experience
.

Requirements

Strong experience with Microsoft Azure services, including understanding their capabilities and limitations and being able to architect and deliver solutions leveraging various Azure platform services
Appropriate certifications in Azure and associated MS technologies
Strong understanding of the cloud architecture patterns and solution design principles
Strong understanding of different attributes for cloud application availability, scalability and ability to propose optimized design for cloud
Have experience in implementing enterprise application using cloud platforms
Experienced in working in agile/devops environment with continuous integration and continuous deployment and application lifecycle management
Excellent articulation and communication skills
New Orleans is the preferred location but will consider other US based candidates

Apply Now &gt;&gt;       

</description>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51153758</referencenumber>
		<title> Assistant Technician</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> Any City</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
		<url>https://jobs.dxc.technology/ShowJob/Id/484813/Assistant-Technician/</url>
		<description>  ›  Assistant Technician - Any City, LA
Assistant Technician - Any City, LA
Apply Now &gt;&gt;    
Requisition ID : 51153758Posting Date : 1-2-2019Category : Technology Field/Customer Support Services GroupLocation : Any City, LA USSchedule : Full TimeJob Description:
Summary

Provides level 2 technical support to end users for personal computers, system communications (LAN/WAN) and/or software applications (packaged products/custom applications to comply with established service level agreements).

Essential Job Functions

Interfaces with end users to resolve basic problems concerning system functions reported through a problem ticket. Reviews information provided and diagnoses issue based on established, routine procedures and scripts. Resolves problems by following basic scripts.
Performs routine install, move, add, and change (ICMS) activities based upon prescribed procedures and processes and as specifically directed.
Maintains currency regarding routine technological, product, process and/or other advances, specifically in line of service, to ensure team performance and achieve team objectives.
Basic Qualifications

High school diploma or G.E.D.
One or more years of technical training in computer field preferred
Zero or more years of technical support experience
Experience working with company products and operating systems
Experience working with solving computer-related technical problems
Experience working with the company escalation policy
Other Qualifications

Basic interpersonal skills to interact with clients and team members
Basic communication skills
Basic organization skills to balance and prioritize work
Basic analytical and problem solving skills
Work Environment

Client or office environment
May require shift or weekend work

Apply Now &gt;&gt;       

</description>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154516</referencenumber>
		<title> Digital Solution Architect IV</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
		<url>https://jobs.dxc.technology/ShowJob/Id/471477/Digital-Solution-Architect-IV/</url>
		<description>  ›  Digital Solution Architect IV - New Orleans, LA
Digital Solution Architect IV - New Orleans, LA
Apply Now &gt;&gt;    
Requisition ID : 51154516Posting Date : 12-14-2018Category : ES - SalesLocation : New Orleans, LA USSchedule : Full TimeJob Description:
ROLE :

•Interact with clients, Product Managers, and Developers in order to envision, model and provide initial models and designs that can be built.•Constantly review the code to ensure the quality of the design by avoiding complexity, advocating clarity and to do this with the team.•Collaborative working with a degree of humility and providing mentoring as required.•Identify business requirements and requirements of the stakeholders on the project.•Design the entire system based on the received requirements.•Choose the System Architecture and each individual component of the system.•Provide Architectural runway to the Squads.•Identify technologies for the implementation of each component and connections between the components.•Control the Architecture during the iteration of the system.
SKILLS:

•10+ years of Experience in IT Industry, defining and solutioning Digital Applications.•Working experience as IOT Architect/Solution Architect/EC Architect/Integration Architect/DevOps Architect•Ability to talk to customers in the language of business, managers of all levels, business analysts and developers in their languages.•Work with different people from different areas, rapidly changing demands or even with changing business environments•Ability to represent an abstract problem in the form of some finite real object of the system, which can be evaluated, designed and developed•Ability to lead the Engineering team, which may be distributed and composed of very different specialists.•Ability to analyze and critically assess problems.•Ability to see the big picture as well as giving attention to the smallest detail.
Apply Now &gt;&gt;       

</description>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154517</referencenumber>
		<title> AWS Architect IV</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
		<url>https://jobs.dxc.technology/ShowJob/Id/471478/AWS-Architect-IV/</url>
		<description>  ›  AWS Architect IV - New Orleans, LA
AWS Architect IV - New Orleans, LA
Apply Now &gt;&gt;    
Requisition ID : 51154517Posting Date : 12-14-2018Category : ES - SalesLocation : New Orleans, LA USSchedule : Full TimeJob Description:
0M904E - Solution Architect IV


Apply Now &gt;&gt;       

</description>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154664</referencenumber>
		<title> Test Engineer IV</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
		<url>https://jobs.dxc.technology/ShowJob/Id/471483/Test-Engineer-IV/</url>
		<description>  ›  Test Engineer IV - New Orleans, LA
Test Engineer IV - New Orleans, LA
Apply Now &gt;&gt;    
Requisition ID : 51154664Posting Date : 12-14-2018Category : ES - EngineeringLocation : New Orleans, LA USSchedule : Full TimeJob Description:
ROLE :

·Responsible for the analysis, delivery, and automation solutions for one or more digital products and/or platforms ·Participates as a member of Agile dev team working with product owner and wider dev teams·Interpret user research in order to make the correct product decisions, noting that users do not always know what they want·Defines, identifies, collects, and organizes detailed information relating to testing requirements.·Interacts with the Product team to gain understanding of the business environment, technical context, and conformance criteria.·Expertise in multiple automated testing processes and tools e.g. Selenium·Stays current on established tools, techniques, and technologies.·Supports knowledge management and collaboration through participation in testing discussions, communities and improving testing collateral through lessons learned.
SKILLS :

 

·Experience in Computer Science or similar technical field of study or equivalent practical experience.·Experience in delivering automated testing services for various project size.·Proficient in testing and development methodologies and their interaction.·Proficient in test automation tooling and keep abreast of the latest trends and processes in the area of automation including Selenium, Cucumber and Gherkin.·Good verbal and written communication skills.·Experience of working in Agile teams delivering digital projects and solutions.·Knowledge of software development technologies preferred(Java, .net)Apply Now &gt;&gt;       

</description>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154514</referencenumber>
		<title> AWS Architect III</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
		<url>https://jobs.dxc.technology/ShowJob/Id/483661/AWS-Architect-III/</url>
		<description>  ›  AWS Architect III - New Orleans, LA
AWS Architect III - New Orleans, LA
Apply Now &gt;&gt;    
Requisition ID : 51154514Posting Date : 12-31-2018Category : ES - SalesLocation : New Orleans, LA USSchedule : Full TimeJob Description:
Role:

Translate concepts into user flows, wireframes, mockups and prototypes that lead to intuitive user experiences.•Facilitate the client’s product vision by researching, conceiving, sketching, prototyping and user-testing experiences for digital products.
Design and deliver wireframes, user stories, user journeys, and mockups optimized for a wide range of devices and interfaces.
Identify design problems and devise elegant solutions.
Make strategic design and user-experience decisions related to core, and new, functions and features.
Take a user-centered design approach and rapidly test and iterate your designs.
Use visual design software to refine illustrations
Demonstrate strong aesthetic skills with the ability to combine various colors, fonts and layouts.
Collaborate with other team members and stakeholders.
Requirements:
5 to 12 years of experience in designing the interface experience for web, mobile, &amp; wearables
Graduated from design school and/or HFI certified is preferred
Collaborate with product managers and developers and define product direction
Understand business requirements and technical limitations
Responsible for defining IA, wireframes, mockups and prototypes
Responsible for combining colors, shapes and typography fonts to improve user experience
Excellent in Sketch, OmniGraffle, Axure, InVision, UXPin, Balsamiq, Framer or similar and Adobe Suite
A solid grasp of user-centered design (UCD), planning and conducting user research, user testing, A/B testing, rapid prototyping, heuristic analysis, usability and accessibility concerns.

Apply Now &gt;&gt;       

</description>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154655</referencenumber>
		<title> Cloud Native Developer</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
		<url>https://jobs.dxc.technology/ShowJob/Id/481083/Cloud-Native-Developer/</url>
		<description>  ›  Cloud Native Developer - New Orleans, LA
Cloud Native Developer - New Orleans, LA
Apply Now &gt;&gt;    
Requisition ID : 51154655Posting Date : 12-26-2018Category : ES - ServicesLocation : New Orleans, LA USSchedule : Full TimeJob Description:
Cloud Native Developer—Senior Level

DXC Technology (NYSE: DXC) is the world’s leading independent, end-to-end IT services company, helping clients harness the power of innovation to thrive on change. Created by the merger of CSC and the Enterprise Services business of Hewlett Packard Enterprise, DXC Technology serves nearly 6,000 private and public sector clients across 70 countries. The company’s technology independence, global talent and extensive partner alliance combine to deliver powerful next-generation IT services and solutions. DXC Technology is recognized among the best corporate citizens globally. For more information, visit www.dxc.technology. 

Role Description

Designs, develops and implements complex cloud-based solutions.  Designs and supports cloud infrastructure, applications and service management. 
Completes plans and specifications to develop, integrate, test and implement solutions and define standards.
Collaborates with internal stakeholders and customers to develop specifications for new cloud-based products and services, applications and solutions. 
Interprets internal or external business issues and recommends solutions and best practices.
Main responsibilities:

Works in conjunction with senior staff to provide advice and counsel to customers on cloud solutions matters.
Participates and supports the creation of the solution architecture and ensures the solution strategy aligns with business strategy.
Develops, installs and configures solutions including platforms and their related components and integration points.  Reviews and revises designs, as appropriate, based on approvals from identified stakeholders.
Designs blueprints and deployment policies that meet customer requirements and specifications.  Revises as necessary to ensure continued support of customer needs.
Creates solutions in relation to, and use of tools, techniques, software, hardware, programming languages and third-party tools/libraries applicable to the solution.
Develops automated solutions and capabilities for deploying tools and technologies.  Implements, as approved, escalating revisions or updates as necessary.
Creates automated functional and integration testing of solutions based upon strategies developed and using approved/designated tests, software and applications. 
Provides leadership and work guidance to less experienced personnel. 
Skills and experience:

AWS Certified Developer- Associate, AWS Certified DevOps Engineer- Professional, MCSE: Cloud Platform and Infrastructure or similar.
Experience with development languages, such as Java, Spring Boot, .NET and other application frameworks, techniques and tools.
Experience in or knowledge of cloud-native development and agile development methodologies.
Experience writing Rest APIs and microservices-based applications. 
Knowledge of system integrations with platforms, such as NoSQL db, Redis Cache, and S3.
Understanding of cloud platforms and providers, such as Google Cloud Platform, Amazon Web Services and Microsoft Azure.
Experience working with private and public clouds.
Experience writing test-driven software development.
Experienced in CI/CD tools including Docker, Github, Chef, Puppet, Jenkins or others.
Ability to pair with a customer’s development team and guide them on leading-edge technologies.
Develop cloud native applications using: Pivotal Cloud Foundry; Kubernetes; .NET particularly Microsoft Azure and/or Java; J2EE; Python; Perl and PHP; Web services and APIs as in RESTful and SOAP; Design patterns and UML; Object-oriented programming; Hibernate and MYBATIS; Ruby on Rails and Scala
Trust, Transform &amp; Thrive with a company whose mission is to leading clients on their digital transformation journeys, DXC Technology will be recognized globally as a force multiplier, enabling clients to seize the opportunities presented by today’s rapidly changing technologies


Apply Now &gt;&gt;       

</description>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154634</referencenumber>
		<title> Business Analyst Senior Level</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
		<url>https://jobs.dxc.technology/ShowJob/Id/480970/Business-Analyst-Senior-Level/</url>
		<description>  ›  Business Analyst Senior Level - New Orleans, LA
Business Analyst Senior Level - New Orleans, LA
Apply Now &gt;&gt;    
Requisition ID : 51154634Posting Date : 12-26-2018Category : ES - ServicesLocation : New Orleans, LA USSchedule : Full TimeJob Description:
This position is located on site in New Orleans, LA, in our Digital Transformation Center next to the Super dome. Relocation assistance available.

DXC’s Delivery organization operates technical and service functions to serve DXC’s diverse client base across a broad range of operational sectors. A data scientist within the Operations Engineering and Excellence (OE&amp;E) team works within DXC to identify, develop and implement opportunities for improving the efficiency and effectiveness of our delivery operations via insights generated from operational data. OE&amp;E’s focus is on solving business problems and thus a core focus of the data science team is on finding the simplest solution that generates the most value for the business. Many of these insights are also evolved into automated data science assets—in collaboration with a DevOps team—that provide continual interactive actionable insights to operations teams.

As a member of the data science team you will work both your local peers and team members located around the world to build, deploy and evolve analytics assets across DXC. You will also work closely with operational leaders within Delivery operations to identify opportunities, available data and ways that data can help in achieving actions with value for our clients and DXC.

Responsibilities:

Participate in the elicitation, documentation, analysis and validation of business processes, systems, and solution requirements.
Research components of solutions to problems.
Produce visualization, user experience and configuration elements of solution design.
Document requirements specifications using high-maturity methods, processes and tools.
Support requirements management and change management processes.
Support aspects of the business cycle, including proposals, feasibility studies, and implementations.
Through self-directed activities act as a liaison between client and technical groups, using superior communication skills to elicit, document, analyze and validate requirements.
Apply industry-specific expertise to recommend and coordinate the development, enhancement, and maintenance of a client's business systems, processes, and products using high-maturity methods, processes and tools.
Combine industry expertise with a thorough understanding of information technology to develop innovative business solutions. Influence the strategic direction of clients.
Lead analysis teams on large projects. Lead requirements management and change management processes.
Direct development of visualization, and user experience elements of solution design.
Develop and maintain internal and external relationships to manage scope, schedule, budgets and expectations.
Lead business studies and present study results to the company and client senior management.
Coordinate and participate in proposals, feasibility studies, and new business development activities.
Leverage industry knowledge and client relationships to assess the business implications of the application of technology to the current and future business environment and to identify new business opportunities. Promote and direct process improvement activities and training of peers and clients.
Required Skillets

Ability to generate actionable insights from messy disconnected datasets, including datasets that may originate in many various forms (e.g., flat files, APIs, database access)
8 or more years experience.
Determination using structured techniques for documentation, analysis, evaluation/ validation.
Decomposition of high-level information into details; abstracting low-level information; distinguishing requests vs needs; distinguishing requirements vs. solutions.
Classifying prioritizing requirements; OO techniques using UML models; ambiguity analysis, ensuring consistent understanding across users, designers and testers; business process modeling of current state and desired future state processes; defining and managing scope and client expectations, requirements change management and traceability; identifying and mitigating risks; applying creativity/ innovation to solving complex problems; building relationships and working collaboratively; developing and communicating a vision for project/ system; providing thought leadership; mentoring; effective verbal/ written communication; preparing and delivering effective presentations; experience in one or more industry domains.
Specialized: Function Point counting; survey design and execution; statistical analysis; developing structured user manuals and training; visualization modeling; business rules modeling; develop and executing acceptance test plans.
Ability to clearly communicate with business units and delivery groups to understand the nature of their business challenges, factors specific to that operation
Ability to quickly generate simple yet power data visualizations to communicate insights
Ability to work closely with others in a fast-paced and collaborative technical setting
Ability to rapidly learn and develop new skills, largely on ones own by staying in tune with the market and emerging technologies and techniques
Strong math and statistical skills and an ability to apply those skills towards generating logical, accurate and meaningful insights from data
An ability to quickly learn the essentials of a new operational team (e.g., a specific account within DXC’s delivery organization) and understand the nuances of tools, processes, data and business requirements that impact actions required to add value for the client and DXC

Desired Qualifications

Typically a Bachelor's degree in a technical or business discipline or equivalent experience and a minimum of 8 years of related experience or a Master's degree and a minimum of 6 years of experience.
Recommended: IIBA CBAP&amp; #8482; (or equivalent) certification obtained.
Ideally, recognized industry- certification.
Proficiency with Python and/or R for use in conducting data analytics
Proficiency with storing and manipulating relational data in databases
Proficiency in handling and working with large datasets, beyond those traditionally handed within relational databases
Proficiency with machine learning techniques and, equally important, when to apply them and when not
Demonstrated track record of generate business insights from data and communicating (ideally via a portfolio of previous work)
Trust, Transform &amp; Thrive with a company whose mission is to leading clients on their digital transformation journeys, DXC Technology will be recognized globally as a force multiplier, enabling clients to seize the opportunities presented by today’s rapidly changing technologies


Apply Now &gt;&gt;       

</description>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154621</referencenumber>
		<title> Business Analyst Manager</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
		<url>https://jobs.dxc.technology/ShowJob/Id/480969/Business-Analyst-Manager/</url>
		<description>  ›  Business Analyst Manager - New Orleans, LA
Business Analyst Manager - New Orleans, LA
Apply Now &gt;&gt;    
Requisition ID : 51154621Posting Date : 12-26-2018Category : ES - ServicesLocation : New Orleans, LA USSchedule : Full TimeJob Description:
DXC Technology (NYSE: DXC) is the world’s leading independent, end-to-end IT services company, helping clients harness the power of innovation to thrive on change. Created by the merger of CSC and the Enterprise Services business of Hewlett Packard Enterprise, DXC Technology serves nearly 6,000 private and public sector clients across 70 countries. The company’s technology independence, global talent and extensive partner alliance combine to deliver powerful next-generation IT services and solutions. DXC Technology is recognized among the best corporate citizens globally. For more information, visit www.dxc.technology.

This position is located on site in New Orleans, LA, in our Digital Transformation Center next to the Super dome. Relocation assistance available.

DXC’s Delivery organization operates technical and service functions to serve DXC’s diverse client base across a broad range of operational sectors. A data scientist within the Operations Engineering and Excellence (OE&amp;E) team works within DXC to identify, develop and implement opportunities for improving the efficiency and effectiveness of our delivery operations via insights generated from operational data. OE&amp;E’s focus is on solving business problems and thus a core focus of the data science team is on finding the simplest solution that generates the most value for the business. Many of these insights are also evolved into automated data science assets—in collaboration with a DevOps team—that provide continual interactive actionable insights to operations teams.

As a member of the data science team you will work both your local peers and team members located around the world to build, deploy and evolve analytics assets across DXC. You will also work closely with operational leaders within Delivery operations to identify opportunities, available data and ways that data can help in achieving actions with value for our clients and DXC.

Responsibilities:

Manages area(s), customer(s), or team(s) of the company employees with well-defined, limited scope, including directing daily work activities/priorities, people recruitment and development, cost management, and direction-setting within the area of responsibility.
Coaches and mentors employee direct reports. May coach and mentor non-direct reports as needed. Manages Focal Point Review (FPR) process for the company employees. Manages team and individual performance.
Advise management and peers on matters of importance to area(s) of responsibility. Propose/influence direction-setting.
Assigns responsibilities, provides direction, leadership, and coaching, removes barriers as needed to enable direct reports to execute their roles and achieve objectives and goals.
Creates a working environment that is conducive to individual growth, high performance, is challenging and rewarding. Achieves diversity and other HR goals.
Establish and manage relationships with customer subject matter experts and appropriate customer management, with an objective of maintaining and building the business.
Direct development of visualization, and user experience elements of solution design.
Develop and maintain internal and external relationships to manage scope, schedule, budgets and expectations.
Lead business studies and present study results to the company and client senior management.
Coordinate and participate in proposals, feasibility studies, and new business development activities.
Leverage industry knowledge and client relationships to assess the business implications of the application of technology to the current and future business environment and to identify new business opportunities. Promote and direct process improvement activities and training of peers and clients.
Required Skillets

Workforce management/development.
(developing) Leadership.
(developing) Influencing Others.
Escalation management, customer relationship-building.
Knowledge of Corporate capabilities and outsourcing industry norms.
Business Analysis and Planning.
General Financial Management/Cost Management.
General Project Management.
In-depth understanding of technology in direct responsibility.
General understanding of related technologies.
(developing) Knowledge of industry and market trends.

Desired Qualifications

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science, Engineering, Business or related field or equivalent work experience.
May hold Master's or advanced degree in related field. Typically 8+ years of relevant experience.
Ideally, recognized industry- certification.
Proficiency with Python and/or R for use in conducting data analytics
Proficiency with storing and manipulating relational data in databases
Proficiency in handling and working with large datasets, beyond those traditionally handed within relational databases
Proficiency with machine learning techniques and, equally important, when to apply them and when not
Demonstrated track record of generate business insights from data and communicating (ideally via a portfolio of previous work)
Trust, Transform &amp; Thrive with a company whose mission is to leading clients on their digital transformation journeys, DXC Technology will be recognized globally as a force multiplier, enabling clients to seize the opportunities presented by today’s rapidly changing technologies


Apply Now &gt;&gt;       

</description>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154536</referencenumber>
		<title> Cloud Native Developer Manager Level</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154530</referencenumber>
		<title> Data Scientist Senior</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154419</referencenumber>
		<title> Professional Analytics ETL/DBA Engineer</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154418</referencenumber>
		<title> Security Architect</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154417</referencenumber>
		<title> UX Engineer</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154416</referencenumber>
		<title> User Interface (UI) Engineer</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154415</referencenumber>
		<title> Software Engineer</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154414</referencenumber>
		<title> Security Engineer</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154413</referencenumber>
		<title> QA Engineer Entry Level/ Early Career</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154412</referencenumber>
		<title> DevOps Engineer Entry Level/Early Career</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154411</referencenumber>
		<title> Data Scientist Entry Level/ Early Career</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154410</referencenumber>
		<title> Business Analyst Entry Level/ Early Career</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154409</referencenumber>
		<title> AWS/Azure Architect Early Career</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154408</referencenumber>
		<title> Analytics ETL/DBA Engineer Entry Level</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154406</referencenumber>
		<title> Full Stack Developer Entry Level/ Early Career</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154513</referencenumber>
		<title> Digital Solution Architect III</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154682</referencenumber>
		<title> Sr. DevOps Engineer V</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154663</referencenumber>
		<title> Test Engineer IV</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154650</referencenumber>
		<title> Big Data Engineer/Architect  Digital Infrastructure</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154619</referencenumber>
		<title> Sr. Project Manager  Digital</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154604</referencenumber>
		<title> Information Security Engineer III</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154542</referencenumber>
		<title> DevOps Engineer IV</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154258</referencenumber>
		<title> Senior UX Designer</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> Convent</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154257</referencenumber>
		<title> Digital Program Manager</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> Convent</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154217</referencenumber>
		<title> Senior Level Software Developer</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> Convent</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154256</referencenumber>
		<title> Ideation Lab Scrum Master</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> Convent</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154683</referencenumber>
		<title> Sr. DevOps Engineer</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154491</referencenumber>
		<title> Digital Solution Architect III</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154543</referencenumber>
		<title> DevOps Engineer IV</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51156922</referencenumber>
		<title> 51000119 – Advisor Recruiting</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> Any City</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>ES_1659120 </referencenumber>
		<title> Technology Consultant III</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>ES_1657769 </referencenumber>
		<title> Entry Level Service Information Developer</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>ES_1657752 </referencenumber>
		<title> Entry Level Software Tester</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>ES_1657750 </referencenumber>
		<title> Entry Level Software Tester</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>ES_1657749 </referencenumber>
		<title> Entry Level Software Tester</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>ES_1657748 </referencenumber>
		<title> Entry Level Software Tester</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>ES_1657747 </referencenumber>
		<title> Entry Level Software Tester</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>ES_1657714 </referencenumber>
		<title> Dev Ops Engineer II</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154651</referencenumber>
		<title> Big Data Engineer</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154620</referencenumber>
		<title> Sr. Project Manager</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154605</referencenumber>
		<title> Information Security Engineer III</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154518</referencenumber>
		<title> Azure Architect IV</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154493</referencenumber>
		<title> Azure Architect III</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154492</referencenumber>
		<title> AWS Architect III</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154407</referencenumber>
		<title> 00S36G  Technology Consultant II</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51154215</referencenumber>
		<title> Solution Architect Manager</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> Convent</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51146564</referencenumber>
		<title> 0M909F  Psls EDS Cons I</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> Convent</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51144829</referencenumber>
		<title> Technology Consultant II</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51135494</referencenumber>
		<title> Software Developer/Engineer III</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<referencenumber>51134941</referencenumber>
		<title> Lead Data Scientist</title>
		<country>United States of America </country>
		<state> Louisiana </state>
		<city> New Orleans</city>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<title/>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<title/>
		<category>Information Technology</category>
	</Row>
</Root>